Finding Aid for the The Andrew Nelson Lytle Addition
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series II. Writings
  - Writings - Essays: Summing Up (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Essays: Summing Up (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Essays: They Took Their Stand (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Essays: They Took Their Stand (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Essays: Unclean Lips (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Essays: Unclean Lips (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Essays: Unidentified (1 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Essays: Unidentified (2 of 2) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Writings - Novels: Bedford Forrest and His Critter Company (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (1 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (2 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (3 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (4 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (5 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (6 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (7 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (8 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (9 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (10 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (11 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (12 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (13 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (14 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Writings - Novels: Southerners and Europeans (15 of 15) (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Writings - Novels: Wake for the Living (1 of 6) (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Writings - Novels: Wake for the Living (2 of 6) (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Writings - Novels: Wake for the Living (3 of 6) (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Writings - Novels: Wake for the Living (4 of 6) (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Writings - Novels: Wake for the Living (5 of 6) (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Writings - Novels: Wake for the Living (6 of 6) (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Writings - Poetry: Sam Dull (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Research Material: Bedford Forrest and His Critter Company (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Research Material: Kristin (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Research Material: Kristin (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Research Material: Wake For The Living (1 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Research Material: Wake For The Living (2 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Research Material: Wake For The Living (3 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Research Material: Wake For The Living (4 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Research Material: Wake For The Living (5 of 5) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Short Story: Mirror, Mirror, on the Wall (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Speeches: Founders' Day Address (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Writings - [Speeches]: Talk for Richmond (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Tribute: Dodson, Mayhew Wilson (Pat) (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Fragments (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Fragments (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Series III. Literary Career
  - Literary Career - Author's Questionnaire: Southerners and Europeans (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Literary Career - Awards (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, Dec. 28, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, May 9, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, Oct. 19, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, Oct. 20, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, Oct. 21, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, Oct. 22, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, April 12, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, June 6, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, September 1983 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, Feb. 24, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, Oct. 15, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, July 7, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Literary Career - Clippings, Feb. 28, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Literary Career - Clippings: No Date (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Literary Career - Clippings: No Date (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Literary Career - Conferences (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Literary Career - Contracts (1 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Literary Career - Contracts (2 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Literary Career - Contracts (3 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Literary Career - Copyright (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Literary Career - Fellowship of Southern Writers (1 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Literary Career - Fellowship of Southern Writers (2 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Literary Career - Fellowship of Southern Writers (3 of 3) (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Literary Career - Fugitive Group (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Literary Career - Institute of Southern Affairs (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Literary Career - Interviews (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Literary Career - Interviews (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Literary Career - Interviews: Corrections (1 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Literary Career - Interviews: Corrections (2 of 2) (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Literary Career - Louisiana State University Press (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Literary Career - Murphy Symposium in Literature and Language (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Literary Career - Productions of Plays (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Literary Career - Publicity (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Literary Career - Publicity: Schedule (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Literary Career - Readings (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Literary Career - Reviews: Eden to Babylon (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Literary Career - Reviews: Hero with the Private Parts (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Literary Career - Reviews: I'll Take My Stand (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Literary Career - Reviews: Kristin, A Reading (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Literary Career - Reviews: The Long Night (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Literary Career - Reviews: Southerners and Europeans (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Literary Career - Reviews: Southerners and Europeans (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Literary Career - Reviews: Wake For The Living (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Literary Career - Royalty Statements: Bedford Forrest & His Critter Co. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Literary Career - Royalty Statements: Hero with the Private Parts (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Literary Career - Royalty Statements: I'll Take My Stand (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Literary Career - Royalty Statements: The Long Night (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Literary Career - Royalty Statements: Southerners and Europeans (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Literary Career - Royalty Statements: The Velvet Horn (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Literary Career - Royalty Statements: Wake For The Living (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Literary Career - Royalty Statements: Fragments (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Literary Career - Sewanee Review (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Literary Career - Fragments (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Series IV. Agrarians
  - Agrarians - (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Agrarians - (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Agrarians - Clippings: Sept. 16, 1989 (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Agrarians - Clippings: Sept. 16, 1989 (2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 28)
- Series V. Academic Career
  - Academic Career - Creative Writing Class Final Exam (1981) (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Academic Career - Creative Writing Class Final Exam (1981) (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Academic Career - Grade Book: English 235 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Academic Career - No Recommendation Written (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Academic Career - Past Exam Questions (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Academic Career - Programs (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Adams, T. - Austin, D. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Baker, R. - Butt, W. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Cameron, D. - Cutler, J. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Dalton, D. - DuPree, D. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Elmore, A. - Griffis, [?] (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Harper, W. - Lewis, L. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Martin, D. - Nardin, R. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Ohl, C. - Puller, J. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written, Quisenberry, R. - Sutton, D. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: Taylor, F. - Townbridge, C. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Academic Career - Recommendations Written: VanDevender, K -Zimmerman,S. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Academic Career - Roll B ook/Grade B ook (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Academic Career - Student Papers (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Academic Career - University of Florida, Gainesville (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Academic Career - University of Florida, Gainesville (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Academic Career - University of the South (Sewanee) (1 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Academic Career - University of the South (Sewanee) (2 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Academic Career - University of the South (Sewanee) (3 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Academic Career - University of the South (Sewanee) (4 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Series VI. Biographical/Personal Papers Box 21
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Biographical (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Biographical (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Biographical: Who's Who in the World (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Business and Financial Records (1 of 6) (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Business and Financial Records (2 of 6) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Business and Financial Records (3 of 6) (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Business and Financial Records (4 of 6) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Business and Financial Records (5 of 6) (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Business and Financial Records (6 of 6) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Clippings, May 22, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Clippings, Dec. 1, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Clippings, Aug. 21, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Clippings, May 2, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Clippings, Sept. 21, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Clippings, Apr. 3, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Clippings: No Date (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Clippings: No Date (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Contacts (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Day Calendar: 1988 (1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Day Calendar: 1988 (2 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Day Calendar, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Day Calendar, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Day Calendar, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Genealogical (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Genealogical (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Genealogical: Wake for the Living (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Genealogical: Wake for the Living (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Guest Book (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Invitations (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Invitations: Prince Andrew and Sarah Ferguson (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Map of Nashville (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Monteagle (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Monteagle Sunday School Assembly (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Monteagle Sunday School Assembly (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Obituary (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Parish Paper of St. John’s Church (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Parish Paper of St. John’s Church (2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Passports (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Photographs (1 of 12) (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Photographs (2 of 12) (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Photographs (3 of 12) (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Photographs (4 of 12) (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Photographs (5 of 12) (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Photographs (6 of 12) (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers – Photographs (7 of 12) (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Photographs (8 of 12) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Photographs (9 of 12) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Photographs (10 of 12) (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Photographs (11 of 12) (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Photographs (12 of 12) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Programs (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Student Days (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Writings about Andrew Lytle (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Fragments (1 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Biographical/Personal Papers - Fragments (2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Series VII. Family Papers
  - Family Papers - Appraisal of Lord Hailsham's Bust (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Family Papers - Diaries, 1896 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Family Papers - Envelopes (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Family Papers - Family Trees (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Family Papers - Financial (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Family Papers - Genealogical (1 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Family Papers - Genealogical (2 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Family Papers - Genealogical (3 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Family Papers - Genealogical Outline of Logan Family (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Family Papers - Lytle, Edna: Master's Degree from L.S.U. (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Family Papers - Lytle, Kate: Clippings (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Family Papers - Lytle, Langdon (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Family Papers - Lytle, Langdon: American Kennel Club (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Family Papers - Lytle, Langdon: Grade Reports (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Family Papers - Writings: Wilson, T.B. (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Family Papers - Writings: Wilson, W.L. (1 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Family Papers - Writings: Wilson, W.L. (2 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Family Papers - Writings: Wilson, W.L. (3 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Family Papers - Writings: Wilson, W.L. (4 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Series VIII. Writings by Others Box 24
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Adams, D. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Barnett, R. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bell, M. (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bell, M. (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bovenizer, D. (1 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bovenizer, D. (2 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bovenizer, D. (3 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (1 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (2 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (3 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (4 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (5 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (6 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (7 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (8 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (9 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (10 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Bradford, M.E. (11 of 11) (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Brenholtz, C. (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Brenholtz, C. (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Burns, D. (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Carlson, T. (1 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Carlson, T. (2 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Carlson, T. (3 of 3) (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Cash, J. (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childers, J. (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childers, J. (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (1 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (2 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (3 of 10) (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (4 of 10) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (5 of 10) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (6 of 10) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (7 of 10) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (8 of 10) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (9 of 10) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Childress, M. (10 of 10) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Chronicles (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Clark, C. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Core, G. (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Core, G. (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Douglass, A. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Dupree, D. (1 of 3) (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Dupree, D. (2 of 3) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Dupree, D. (3 of 3) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Fletcher, J. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Foata, A. (1 of 4) (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Foata, A. (2 of 4) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Foata, A. (3 of 4) (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Foata, A. (4 of 4) (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Gerber, M. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Goddard, H. (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Gould, W.S. and Gould, C.B. (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Gould, W.S. and Gould, C.B. (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Graham, S. (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Graham, S. (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Graves, J. (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Hall, J. (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Hansberger III, F. (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Hart, J. (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Hetrick, L. (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Huber, L. and Wilson, S. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Hudson, D. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Hunter, J.T. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Irvin, B. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Jones, D. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Jones, M. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kaemmerling, M. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (1 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (2 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (3 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (4 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (5 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (6 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (7 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (8 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (9 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (10 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (11 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (12 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (13 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (14 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (15 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (16 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (17 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kirk, R. (18 of 18) (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Kotker, N. (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Lapham, L. (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Leonhirth, J. (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Lucas, M. (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Lynch, A. (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Meyers, J. (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (1 of 9) (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (2 of 9) (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (3 of 9) (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (4 of 9) (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (5 of 9) (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (6 of 9) (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (7 of 9) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (8 of 9) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Middleton, D. (9 of 9) (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Mills, W.H. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Montgomery, M. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Myers, L. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: O'Connor, F. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Oras, A. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Owsley, F. and Owsley, H. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Owsley, F. (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Owsley, F. (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Owsley, H.C. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Peters, M. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Pratt, W. (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Writings By Others - Identified: Pratt, W. (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 18)